freecreditreports360.com 2018-08-18

# One Technologies

One Technologies – Privacy Policy
Last updated: May 10, 2018
OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY
We use the terms “you” and “your” to include any person who accesses the Sites, as defined in the
Term and Conditions, or purchases any product or service offered on the Sites (the “Services”) for
any amount of time. We use the terms “we”, “us” and “our” to refer to One Technologies, LLC (the
“Company”), which owns and/or operates this website, and our employees, members, officers,
directors, partners, affiliated entities, representatives, attorneys and agents.
We understand how important your privacy is to you, so we are committed to assuring your privacy.
This page outlines all of the steps we take to protect your privacy, and what we do with the
information that you provide to us through our website.
What information do we collect?
In order to provide you with our services, we collect two types of information about our users:
Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.
Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of
who you are. When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering for a
membership, ordering a product or service, or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide
certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely
optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, we
may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address
(including zip code), social security number, email address, employer, job title and department,
telephone, mobile telephone and facsimile numbers, assets, liabilities and other personal identifying
information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit
card number. Depending upon the product or service, if you do not provide the requested
information, you may not be able to obtain the product or service you want. You should be aware
that if you enter any personal information during the information request process and then click the
“submit” or any other button on that page, the information you have entered will be transmitted to us,
even though you may not complete the process on subsequent pages.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify a
specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our site in
several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated
basis. This information may include the website's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just
came from, which URL you go to next, what browser you are using and your Internet Protocol ("IP")
address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web.
An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet
Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP
protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP

address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the
web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in
order for users to communicate on the Internet.
Protecting your information
We use SSL-encryption technology when transferring and receiving consumer data on our websites
to protect your personal information. We have partnered with Symantec or other equally reliable
encryption services to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have
collected from you. The servers on which we store Personally Identifiable Information are kept in a
secure environment. However, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can
be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable
Information, you acknowledge that there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet that are
beyond our control; the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged
between you and us through this site cannot be guaranteed; and any such information and data may
be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party. We make no warranty, express, implied or
otherwise, that we will prevent unauthorized access to your private information.
How do we use information we collect?
We will use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our site, fill orders,
improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze site use, improve our product
and service offerings, and customize our site's content, layout and services. We may use Personally
Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative
notices. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot
problems and enforce our agreements with you, including our Terms and Conditions and this Privacy
Policy. Your information may also be used by us or by third parties to whom we transfer it to provide
the products or services you have requested.
Some of our products may include alert emails that are sent on a daily, weekly or monthly basis.
These emails are part of your membership and cannot be disabled. In order to receive the most up-
to-date notifications and alerts, your email address must be accurate in your profile.
Some of our products may include text alert messages that are sent on a daily, weekly or monthly
basis. These texts are optional and you can change your settings at any time in your portal. In order
to receive the most up-to-date notifications and alerts, your mobile telephone number must be
accurate in your profile.
When you use our site, we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize
your use of our site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer's
hard drive (if your web browser permits) and can later be retrieved to identify you to us. The cookies
make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure
site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site
may not work properly in that case.
We may use an outside ad serving company to display banner advertisements on our site. As part of
their service, they will place a separate cookie on your computer. We and our third-party ad server

may collect and use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP address,
browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with
your server, and whether you responded to a particular ad.
With whom do we share your information?
We may sell, trade, rent or otherwise transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to others. We
provide the products and services offered on our website through contractual arrangements with
affiliates, service providers and other third parties. We and such third parties use your Personally
Identifiable Information to operate our sites and to deliver their products and services. For example,
we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for
products and services purchased on this site, release your Personally Identifiable Information to the
third party that will provide the products or services that you ordered, and provide order information
to third parties that help us provide customer service. We will encourage our service providers to
adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by our
service providers is governed by the privacy policies of those service providers, and is not subject to
our control.
We may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic
patterns and related site information to third-party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any
Personally Identifiable Information.
Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally
Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally
Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena, or to cooperate with a law
enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those
who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies
any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.
We also allow some of our employees and independent contractors access to both Personally
Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information to enable them to assist us with
our business and provide the services and products that we offer to you. We endeavor to have all
such employees and contractors sign nondisclosure or confidentiality agreements with us in order to
protect your information.
From time to time, we make the email addresses of those who provide them to us available to other
reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you supply
us with your postal address online, you may receive mailings from other reputable companies.
In the event that you unsubscribe from marketing email communications, we may share your email
address with our compliance vendor or approved marketing partners to prevent you from receiving
additional offers.
Privacy policies of third parties
When you sign up for services through our site, keep in mind that you may be interacting with a third
party that operates under its own privacy and security policies. Except as otherwise discussed in this

Privacy Policy, this document only addresses our use and disclosure of information we collect from
you. Other sites accessible through our site, and companies to whom your information is transferred,
have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult
each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.
Additionally, other companies that place advertising on our site may collect information about you
when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this
collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions
about their use of the information that they collect. You should also be aware that unsubscribing
from us will not automatically unsubscribe you from third parties.
Updating your account information
Corrections or updates to your account information, including your email address, mailing address
and credit card information, can be made through the “Account Info” section of your member
account. If necessary, other corrections or updates to your information can be made by contacting a
Customer Care representative during our Customer Care hours.
Business transitions
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, customer
information (both Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable Information) may be one of
the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that we, or substantially all of our assets, are
acquired, such customer information will be included within the transferred assets.
Opting out
If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional offers, you may "opt out" of receiving
these communications by opting out on our unsubscribe page or by clicking here to unsubscribe.
Our membership products may include alert emails or other informational emails that are sent on a
daily, weekly or monthly basis. These transactional emails are part of your membership and cannot
be disabled for persons who are members of these products.
Surveys and contests
From time to time, our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these
surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and
therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as
name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code and age level). Contact
information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for
the purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our Site.
Changes to our policy
We may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so
please review it frequently. When we do, we will post those changes on this page and update the
effective date so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and under
what circumstances we disclose it. You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of our site Terms
and Conditions, and by accessing or using our site, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and

conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. You
acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to maintain a valid email address as a registered
user, review this site and this Policy periodically, and to be aware of any modifications. Your use of
the site after such modifications will constitute your acknowledgment of the modified Policy, and your
agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy.
Miscellaneous/contact information
You must be at least 18 years old to use this site. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose
Personally Identifiable Information about visitors who are under 18 years of age.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site or your dealings with
this site, please contact us at:
Attn: Customer Care
4447 North Central Expressway
Suite 110, PMB 406
Dallas, TX 75205
The Customer Care team is available to answer your questions via phone seven days a
week.
Live representatives are available during the following hours:
Monday through Friday, 8AM to 8PM CST
Saturday, 8AM to 5PM CST
Sunday, Noon to 6PM CST
